[Music]
what is term life insurance simply put
all types of life insurance can help
provide your loved ones with Financial
Security when you die one common type of
life insurance is called term life
insurance how does term life insurance
work term coverage provides protection
for a fixed payment amount for a given
number of years this could be 10 15 or
20 or more years you can choose the
amount of time you need what happens if
you die during this set time period Then
your beneficiaries the people or person
you want to leave money behind to will
get a tax-free death benefit the death
benefit refers to the amount of money
your beneficiary gets when you die the
exact amount they get depends on how
much coverage you buy your beneficiaries
can then use the money from that benefit
for any reason for example they can use
it to pay debts the mortgage or rent
child care costs
tuition costs funeral costs living
expenses and
more why choose term life insurance
because of its affordability and
flexibility term life insurance can be a
good solution to help you manage risk
while providing for your
dependence but its true value lies in
the peace of mind it can offer the
Assurance your loved ones can be
financially supported at a time when
they need it most for more tips and
tools visit at sunlife.ca
[Music]